Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Fifth Young Lord has been found by the Empress Dowager.
She has already issued an imperial decree.
She ordered the Imperial Guards to escort him back.
Will Beile really give the Seven Stars Lamp
and He Fuyi to the Empress Dowager?
Then his agreement with you, Prince,
and our own promise would be abandoned.
Fifth Young Lord wouldn't stir up trouble for no reason.
After all, the Seven Stars Lamp
is just a legendary artifact.
If used well,
reward.
But if misused or broken,
the first to lose his head
will be Baiyintu.
Old Buddha has summoned him by decree.
And sent Imperial Guards to escort him.
Even if Fifth Young Lord wants to hide,
he has no chance now.
Fifth Young Lord seems sly usually,
but he has no grand ambitions.
And in the whirlpool of power,
he struggles to keep afloat.
He just wants a peaceful life.
But this time, this hot potato
has somehow landed on him.
Maybe it's because Fifth Young Lord
is quite skilled.
Anyway, no matter what,
the Seven Stars Lamp
must never fall into the Empress Dowager's hands.
Oh, right.
I, the Prince,
have drafted a secret letter in advance.
You must secretly
deliver it to Fifth Young Lord at Beile Mansion.
Also,
when the time comes,
arrange some men.
Find an opportunity
to create some chaos.
It will help He Fuyi escape.
If anything goes wrong,
destroy the Seven Stars Lamp
and kill He Fuyi.
We've already gathered the old lady's Spiritual Qi.
The seventh Big Dipper star
has also been lit.
But the Seven Stars Lamp
shows no reaction.
I don't feel anything either.
Maybe it's just like before.
Lighting it alone isn't enough.
We need more spiritual light and Spiritual Qi
to fill it up.
Right.
After lighting the sixth Big Dipper star,
we gathered two more people's Spiritual Qi
to light the seventh star.
So it seems
we need more time
to collect more people's dreams.
But now it's difficult.
Of all times, Old Buddha is watching us now.
And brought so many people.
Now we really can't run.
Can't hide either.
It's fine.
If worst comes to worst, just hand me over.
Anyway,
not just anyone can activate the Seven Stars Lamp.
The Seven Stars Lamp is an ancient artifact.
For hundreds and thousands of years,
who knows how many hands it's passed through.
But there are many legends about it.
Plenty, in fact.
Whether it's Zhuge Liang who divided the realm,
or Liu Bowen who unified the land,
they only knew a little about it.
The reason I could summon A Qi
was pure chance.
So even if you take me and the lamp to the palace,
probably nothing will happen.
If only that were true.
I'm just afraid Old Buddha
has too many talented people around her.
In the end,
it's all my fault.
I shouldn't have come to you.
It's not your fault.
I was the one who spread the word.
If not you, it would have been someone else.
The situation isn't so bad now.
Seven Big Dipper stars
are all lit.
With two more Spiritual Qi at most,
I can survive.
Also,
Before Shen Changfeng died, he said
What did he say?
I don't know either.
His identity
is very mysterious.
Back then, your father protected you and fought your way out.
He personally hunted you down.
I only know he was a cultivator—
A cultivator...
Now that you mention it,
I do remember
when my father took me fleeing,
someone chased us from behind.
I definitely saw him.
Do you remember what he looked like?
He was masked.
It's normal not to remember.
After all, at that time
you were only seven.
But
from when my father fled with me
to when I woke up below the cliff,
such a long stretch of memory
I can't remember any of it.
Did I hit my head too hard?
I used to think
it was because I was young,
plus the urgent situation,
and the trauma.
It's normal not to remember.
But now that I think about it,
this missing memory
doesn't seem so simple.
It can't be
someone opened your head
and stole that memory, right?
Actually,
I've always wanted to tell you something.
About our first meeting?
What are you talking about?
It was that day at Shen Changfeng's house.
What do you want to say?
I want to say,
if the missing memory
really wasn't an accident,
then the day you fell off the cliff and were in danger,
the first person you saw when you woke up
is the most suspicious.
The one who harmed you
was me?
The reason you suspect my master
Is this the only reason?
There’s more.
It’s nothing.
Whether it’s memory loss
or so-called eyewitness accounts,
they’re just our own speculations.
If my master
really wanted to steal the Seven Stars Lamp
and was the one who wiped out my family,
then the moment he saw me,
he should have taken the Seven Stars Lamp.
He had no reason to save my life.
Even less reason to teach me his skills.
I know.
He,
was with you for ten whole years.
He’s the master you trust most.
So this is your home.
How is it?
Not bad, right?
Our Beile Mansion
among all the Beiles in Four-Nine City,
is truly one of a kind.
Beile Lord.
Please wash your hands first.
It’s pretty nice.
Now it seems
you really look like a noble.
It’s been hard on you.
All along the way,
you’ve endured hardship with me.
What’s wrong?
Don’t move.
There’s something on you.
Be careful tonight.
Leave as soon as you get a chance.
Don’t trust anyone.
What’s wrong?
When I get close to someone,
my heart starts racing.
Logically speaking,
this feeling
should be attraction.
Right?
Zhang Wei and his men are guarding Beile Mansion.
And they’re the best fighters
in the Imperial Guards.
If we reach a stalemate,
we have only one goal.
That’s the Seven Stars Lamp.
If we can’t get it,
we destroy it.
Urgent summons from the Empress Dowager.
Deliver.
Oral decree from the Empress Dowager.
To Dorobele,
Baiyintu,
enter the palace at once.
for an audience.
Only me is summoned.